hi there and welcome to cardup today I'm
going to explain how you can pay your
manual life insurance premium with
either your credit card or a bank
transfer let's get started first step
navigate to the website
www. card
up.co click personal in the top left
corner this will take you to a website
page that explains exactly how cardup
works when you're ready in the top right
hand corner click sign up on this page
all you have to do is enter your email
address and password accept the terms
and conditions and log
in once you've logged in you'll be taken
to your cardup dashboard this is where
you'll be able to track all the past and
upcoming manual life payments that you
have scheduled but first we need to
verify your account click on create
payment and will'll automatically
redirect you to enter your sing pass
information you can choose whether to
use sing pass or manual let's use sing
pass at this point you'll be redirected
to the official sing pass website it's
your choice whether you want to scan the
QR code to log in or use your ID and
password follow the steps and sing pass
will automatically send your information
to cardup don't worry all your private
data is completely secure we'll verify
your details and in just a few minutes
you'll be ready to to set up a payment
now it's time to set up your first
payment to manual life go back to your
cardup dashboard and click create
payment on this page you'll see the wide
variety of payment categories that you
can pay with cardup from rent and condo
fees to your parking and electricity
bill let's click on
insurance we've already loaded manual
life's payment details into our system
so simply type in manual life and you'll
see the option popup select the USD
option now we're at the page where you
have to enter your payment details
starting at the top you have to enter
what is the USD amount you need to send
to manual life cup will automatically
calculate what that value is in
Singapore dollars and any applicable
fees there's information buttons along
the way that explain why there are fees
at the bottom you'll see the total
amount that you will need to pay in
Singapore dollars
in order to settle your USD insurance
premium let's move on in the next
section you'll decide which payment
method you want to use to pay for your
insurance premium you have two
options option one you can pay by credit
card you can use any Visa Mastercard
American Express or union pay credit
card or option two you can pay with bank
transfer let's start with bank transfer
one of the first things you have to tell
us is what is the source of funds this
is to make sure that we know that there
aren't any fraudulent transactions
happening simply click the drop- down
menu and choose the one that makes the
most sense to you I'm going to choose
employment because my salary puts the
funds in my bank
account in the next section you can
actually skip past it you'll be making a
one-time payment because this is in
USD then enter your policy reference
number and choose what the purpose of
the payment is you'll see insurance
premiums as one of the drop- down
options when you're ready click
continue now it's time for you to review
your payment details in the box you'll
see a summary of how much money you're
sending how much money manual life will
receive and any applicable fees make
sure you read through it carefully and
make sure you agree to the terms and
conditions when you're ready click
create
payment now there's only one more step
to go
because you've chosen bank transfer you
now need to make sure that you transfer
the funds that you owe into the provided
bank account by the provided due date in
this case I have to make the transfer by
9:00 a.m. on the 9th of June
20123 the bank that I need to transfer
to has been clearly
provided once everything is ready you
can either go back to payments which
will take you back to your dashboard or
you can create another
payment now I'm going to demonstrate how
to to use your credit card to pay your
manual life insurance premium you have
the option to pay by Visa Mastercard
American Express or union pay if it's
your first time click the drop- down
menu and click add credit card and
simply enter your credit card
details after you've added your credit
card details all the information will be
saved simply click the card you want to
use and move on to the next stage
if you choose to pay by credit card you
will see that a small fee is applied we
charge this fee in order to make sure
that your transaction is secure and
enable you to earn rewards on a payment
type that traditionally doesn't accept
credit cards the benefit to you is that
you'll be able to earn card rewards such
as air miles or cashback let's click
continue on the final page you'll be
able to review everything about your
payment making sure that the amount of
money that you're sending manual life is
correct and the day that we will charge
your credit card read the terms and
conditions and click create
payment when you're ready return to your
cardup dashboard homepage by click in
the top left corner here you'll see the
payment that you've just set up if you
set up a bank transfer at first the
status will say awaiting funds don't
forget to make the bank transfer by the
payment due date after we cut up his re
received your funds the status will turn
to scheduled and finally after the due
date will turn to complete if you set up
your payment via credit card you'll see
that listed in the column payment method
on the left hand side under status at
first it will say scheduled and then on
the payment due date it will turn to
complete and there you've have it you've
successfully set up your insurance
premium payment to manual life Singapore
if if you ever want to know about the
status of one of your payments you can
always log into your cardup account and
look at the status column we'll also
send you emails every time you set up a
payment and once it's completed remember
you can always log in and pay for any
other type of bill with cardup including
your rent mortgage and car
bills if you have any questions please
reach out to us we're more than happy to
help thanks for watching when you're
ready head over to to our website card
up.co to sign up and get started today